[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name Zimbabwes capital which is an independent city equivalent to a province.", "correct_answer": "Harare", "incorrect_answers": ["Cairo", "Rome", "Tunis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is the smallest vertebrate?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Mammals", "Reptiles", "Amphibians"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these would not cause a muscle cramp?", "correct_answer": "being overweight", "incorrect_answers": ["dehydration", "low blood sugar", "extreme cold"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many bony plates did a Stegosaurus have embedded on its back?", "correct_answer": "17", "incorrect_answers": ["11", "9", "15"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In astrology Saturn is believed to be the planetary ruler of which sign?", "correct_answer": "Capricorn", "incorrect_answers": ["Pisces", "Cancer", "Sagittarius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does a la crecy  mean?", "correct_answer": "Served with carrots", "incorrect_answers": ["Served with butter", "Served with sauce", "Served with cheese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Sam and Lucys favorite book in the movie I Am Sam?", "correct_answer": "Green Eggs  Ham", "incorrect_answers": ["Horton Hears a Who! Can You?", "The Cat in the Hat", "Hop On Pop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous California prison was home to Charles Manson?", "correct_answer": "Folsom", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bastille", "Sing Sing", "Joliet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the 1941 movie starring Humphrey Bogart and Mary Astor in which a private eye is searching for a murderer and a jewelled bird?", "correct_answer": "The Maltese Falcon", "incorrect_answers": ["Shanghai Express", "Duck Soup", "Sabotage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many different types of animals were used in the movie Eight Below (not including the dogs)?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "4", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I think we need a bigger boat... is a phrase belonging to which of these films?", "correct_answer": "Jaws", "incorrect_answers": ["Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Mans Chest", "Open Waters", "Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When you give a diamond to someone, it represents this.", "correct_answer": "Everlasting love", "incorrect_answers": ["Affection", "Everlasting friendship", "Appreciation"]}]